#### MOCHAMAD GALIH RAMDHANI

mcgalihramdhan@gmail.com | 081906795257 | linkedin.com/in/mcgalih Tangerang, Indonesia

#### **Profile Summary:**

Hello, I graduated from UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta majoring in Physics with a focus on Instrumentation Physics. Experience in analyzing experimental data has leverage my skills in identifying problems and troubleshooting capabilities. I have an understanding of hardware (computer and robot hardware) and software (Arduino, Python) based on my experience in disassembling and designing hardware and also creating program algorithms.

#### **Experiences**

#### Ekspedisi 2018 event, HIMAFI UIN Jakarta - Tangerang Selatan, Indonesia

Agu 2018 - Jan 2019

Graphic Designer

- Create an instagram posts
- Create a nametag design
- Create a banner design

### Pusat Laboratorium Terpadu UIN Jakarta - Tangerang Selatan, Indonesia

Feb 2021 - Dec 2021

Laboratory Assistant

- Checking and calibrating the tools before doing experiments
- Leading and teaching the student how to operate and achieve the result as cited in the practitioner module for several courses
- Correcting and assessing student experimental reports

#### Education

#### UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta - Tangerang Selatan, Indonesia

Mei 2017 - Jan 2023

Bachelor of Science - 3.52/4.00

- Concentrate in Instrumentation Physics
- Member of Himpunan Mahasiswa Fisika (HIMAFI) UIN Jakarta
- Member of Himpunan Qari dan Qariah Mahasiswa (HIQMA) UIN Jakarta

#### **Skills and Certifications**

#### Skills:

- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PPT)
- Object oriented programming (Arduino, Python)
- Web design (HTML, CSS, Javascript)
- Graphic design (Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro)

#### **Certifications:**

- Participants
   RevoU Mini Course Digital Marketing: Issued Jan 2023 no expiration date
- Participants
   RevoU Fundamental Course Software Engineering: Issued Mar 2023 no expiration date
- Participants
   RevoU Mini Course Data Analytics: Issued Apr 2023 no expiration date

#### **Portfolio**

Auto Move Charity Box, Arduino-based Robot

A thesis project about a mosque charity box that can move automatically. The charity box moves along the track line, place a hand in front of it to stop and behind it to move again.







Charity Box with a Card Security System, Arduino-based Robot

An internship project about a mosque charity box with a card security system. Charity box can only be opened with a correct card where the said card can be defined with Arduino program.









# Mini Course

### **MOCHAMAD RAMDHANI**

Has been awarded a certificate of completion for the

**Intro to Digital Marketing** 

a 1-week certified online course offered by RevoU



Matteo Sutto
CEO & Co-founder
PT Revolusi Cita Edukasi



### **Fundamental Course**

### **MOCHAMAD RAMDHANI**

Has been awarded a certificate of attendance for the

Intro to Software Engineering

a 2-weeks certified online course offered by RevoU



Matteo Sutto
CEO & Co-founder
PT Revolusi Cita Edukasi



# **Mini Course**

### **MOCHAMAD RAMDHANI**

Has been awarded a certificate of completion for the

## Intro to Data Analytics

a 2-weeks certified online course offered by RevoU



Matteo Sutto
CEO & Co-founder
PT Revolusi Cita Edukasi